Recount the days in this neon cage Smiling for
the cameras on a plastic stage They turn those
heads up, drown the sound But you can't keep a
good thing down We're gonna break the walls
tonight, yeah Turn up the volume, hit the light
No more whispers, time to shout The engine's
roaring,
let it out.
Head on the glass, try to the suits who think
they're the boss. This guitar is loaded, it's
ready to scream. Waking up from their pretty
dream We're gonna break the walls tonight, yeah
Turn up the volume, hit the light
No more whispers, time to shout The angels roar
for every kid who feels the same trapped in a
world playing their game this one's for you this
one's for me time to be free
We're gonna break the walls tonight.
Turn up the volume, hit the light.
No more whispers. Time to shout. The engine
roaring.
Let it out.
Let it out!
Break the walls! Come on!